convergys.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy & Legal Statement | Convergys

Convergys intends to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. We are committed to protecting your personal privacy. We provide this privacy policy to explain the type of information we collect on our Web site, www.convergys.com. This policy also explains the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

### The Information We Collect

This policy applies to all information submitted on this Web site. In general, you can visit convergys.com without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you (such as your name and address) to be able to provide you with the information, service or product you have requested. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit our site. We analyze this data for trends and statistics about site traffic. We also may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We, or one of our business partners, may from time to time also ask for other personal information via the Internet. We may use this information to correspond with you to process an order or to provide you with a subscription to an online newsletter, for example. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. Users may choose to opt-out of receiving future e-mail or mailings by following the unsubscribe procedures below.

### The Way We Use Information

Convergys.com provides you with the opportunity to register on the site through our Request for Information form. When you register with our Web site, you can elect to receive information and updates on our products and services.

We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail that we receive, and we may use return e-mail to send you other information.

We use information that you provide (individual and aggregate) to better design our Web site and to enhance our marketing strategy and our products. One method through which this Web site collects aggregate information is the collection of IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from this Web site, our servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us. To the extent such information is shared with third parties, please see "Our Privacy Practices With Third Parties," below.

Occasionally, you may have the opportunity to forward pages or information on our Web site to friends or colleagues. The information you provide to facilitate this e-mail communication is collected by Convergys to correspond with you to process an order, to process a request for information, or to provide you with other forms of information, such as an online newsletter.

### Convergys Unsubscribe Policy

By registering on the Convergys Web site, visitors allow Convergys to use their personal identifiable information in accordance with the terms of Convergys’ privacy policy and legal statement.

Convergys provides site visitors with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving updates on Convergys products and services, newsletters and other promotional materials. You may choose not to be contacted in the future if you do not wish to receive any information with respect to Convergys and our products and services. Visitors may unsubscribe at any time, by sending an e-mail to [marketing@convergys.com ](mailto:marketing@convergys.com)or by calling 1-800-344-3000 and stating the request. Convergys' mailing address may be found on our Contact Us Web page. Visitors should provide Convergys with their name, address, other relevant information (e.g., phone number, e-mail address) and the name of the programs from which they wish to be removed.

Convergys will use reasonable efforts to honor opt-out requests as soon as possible. If after a reasonable time a visitor is still receiving e-mail from Convergys, the visitor should contact [corporate.compliance@convergys.com](mailto:corporate.compliance@convergys.com).

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer's hard drive when you visit a Web site. We use cookies to better tailor our site and our products/services to your interests and needs. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities or to improve your user experience by remembering the information that you have already provided to us. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not voluntarily provided by you (i.e., during membership registration or a contest entry). The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most Web sites. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent so that you can flush them from your browser if you object to their presence.

### Our Privacy Practices with Third Parties

One of our business partners may from time to time also ask for other personal information via the Internet. They may use this information to correspond with you to process an order or to provide you with a subscription to an online newsletter, for example. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. Users may choose to opt-out of receiving future e-mail or mailings by e-mailing us at web.services@convergys.com.

Occasionally, we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with our business and alliance partners. Other than our business and alliance partners, we do not provide personal identifiable information to any third party for any purpose whatsoever.

### Links to Other Sites

Users should be aware that when you are on this Web site you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There may be links to other sites that take you outside our service; for example, links to business/alliance partners and trade show companies. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. If the Convergys Web site links you to any third-party Web site, we make no representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their Privacy Policy.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk.

### Restrictions on Use of Site

Convergys authorizes you to copy the materials published on our Web site (the "Materials") exclusively for non-commercial use by you personally or within your organization. The design and layout of the site are specifically excluded from the Materials. No other use of the Materials is authorized. In consideration of this authorization, you agree that any copy of the Materials (or any portion of the Materials) that you make shall retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained herein or therein.

### Property Rights

The products, technology, and/or processes described in this site may be the subject of intellectual property rights reserved by Convergys or other third parties. Nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring to you in any manner, whether by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license, title, or ownership of or to any intellectual property right of Convergys or any third party.

### General Disclaimer

The Materials have been compiled by Convergys from internal and external sources. However, while we have attempted to provide accurate information on convergys.com, no representation is made or warranty given as to the completeness or accuracy of the Materials. In particular, you should be aware that the Materials may be incomplete, may contain errors, or may have become out of date. You should therefore verify information obtained from this Web site before you take any action upon it.

### Stream Global Services, Inc. US-EU Safe Harbor Participation

Convergys has acquired Stream Global Services, Inc., a company that participates in the US-EU Safe Harbor Privacy Arrangement ("Safe Harbor"). To review the Stream Global Services Safe Harbor Privacy Policy, please click here: <http://www.stream.com/privacypolicy.html>. For any questions about Stream's Safe Harbor privacy practices, please contact us at [corporate.compliance@convergys.com](mailto:corporate.compliance@convergys.com).

### Disclosure: Forward-Looking Statements

Some of the Materials may contain projections or other forward-looking statements regarding future events or the future financial or technical performance of Convergys. We wish to caution you that these statements are only projections and that actual events or results may differ materially. The Material are subject to and qualified by the documents we file from time to time with the Securities and Exchange Commission. These documents contain and identify important factors that could cause the actual results to differ materially from those contained in our projections or forward-looking statements including, among others, substantial capital requirements; development of effective internal processes and systems; the ability to attract and retain high quality employees; changes in the overall economy; technology; the number and size of competitors in its markets; law and regulatory policy; and the mix of products and services offered in the company's target markets and circumstances of force majeure, including acts of war or acts of terrorism. We have no current intention of updating any projections or forward-looking statements that may be contained in the Materials.

### Copyright Policy

Under US law, Convergys, the Convergys logo and Outthinking Outdoing are service marks of Convergys, Atlys, Catalys, Infinys and the Wizard are registered trademarks, and Geneva is a trademark of Convergys Corporation. Convergys refers to Convergys Corporation and its wholly owned subsidiaries. All other trademarks and names are the property of their respective owners. The contents of the Convergys Web site are protected by applicable copyright laws. No permission is granted to copy, distribute, modify, post or frame any text, graphics, video, audio, software code, or user interface design or logos. ALL INFORMATION AND CONTENT ON OUR WEB SITE ARE SUBJECT TO APPLICABLE STATUTES AND REGULATIONS, FURNISHED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.

© 2015 Convergys Corporation. All rights reserved.
